[{"subjectID":"yg56lwljnr","prolificID":"6719280d44c996e04f9a5475","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25171d097020dac2f28","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980285462,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"75","question":"If you opened a restaurant, what would it be like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":20172,"timeElapsed":88047},{"subjectID":"yg56lwljnr","prolificID":"6719280d44c996e04f9a5475","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25171d097020dac2f28","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980301126,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"75","question":"If you opened a restaurant, what would it be like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":15659,"timeElapsed":103710},{"subjectID":"yg56lwljnr","prolificID":"6719280d44c996e04f9a5475","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25171d097020dac2f28","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980321894,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"75","question":"If you opened a restaurant, what would it be like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":20763,"timeElapsed":124479},{"subjectID":"yg56lwljnr","prolificID":"6719280d44c996e04f9a5475","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25171d097020dac2f28","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980327166,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"75","question":"If you opened a restaurant, what would it be like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":5266,"timeElapsed":129751},{"subjectID":"yg56lwljnr","prolificID":"6719280d44c996e04f9a5475","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25171d097020dac2f28","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980340885,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"75","question":"If you opened a restaurant, what would it be like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":20,"rt":13715,"timeElapsed":143470},{"subjectID":"yg56lwljnr","prolificID":"6719280d44c996e04f9a5475","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25171d097020dac2f28","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980347046,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"75","question":"If you opened a restaurant, what would it be like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":19,"rt":6156,"timeElapsed":149631},{"subjectID":"yg56lwljnr","prolificID":"6719280d44c996e04f9a5475","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25171d097020dac2f28","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980354485,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"75","question":"If you opened a restaurant, what would it be like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":2,"rt":7435,"timeElapsed":157070},{"subjectID":"yg56lwljnr","prolificID":"6719280d44c996e04f9a5475","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25171d097020dac2f28","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980370716,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"75","question":"If you opened a restaurant, what would it be like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":11,"rt":16227,"timeElapsed":173301},{"subjectID":"yg56lwljnr","prolificID":"6719280d44c996e04f9a5475","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25171d097020dac2f28","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980376405,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"75","question":"If you opened a restaurant, what would it be like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":49,"rt":5687,"timeElapsed":178990},{"subjectID":"yg56lwljnr","prolificID":"6719280d44c996e04f9a5475","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25171d097020dac2f28","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980389933,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"108","question":"What are some pieces of media (books, movies, music, etc.) that have influenced how you think or see the world?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":11882,"timeElapsed":192518},{"subjectID":"yg56lwljnr","prolificID":"6719280d44c996e04f9a5475","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25171d097020dac2f28","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980399061,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"108","question":"What are some pieces of media (books, movies, music, etc.) that have influenced how you think or see the world?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":9124,"timeElapsed":201646},{"subjectID":"yg56lwljnr","prolificID":"6719280d44c996e04f9a5475","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25171d097020dac2f28","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980406840,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"108","question":"What are some pieces of media (books, movies, music, etc.) that have influenced how you think or see the world?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":7775,"timeElapsed":209425},{"subjectID":"yg56lwljnr","prolificID":"6719280d44c996e04f9a5475","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25171d097020dac2f28","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980411325,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"108","question":"What are some pieces of media (books, movies, music, etc.) that have influenced how you think or see the world?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":4481,"timeElapsed":213910},{"subjectID":"yg56lwljnr","prolificID":"6719280d44c996e04f9a5475","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25171d097020dac2f28","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980421709,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"108","question":"What are some pieces of media (books, movies, music, etc.) that have influenced how you think or see the world?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":34,"rt":10380,"timeElapsed":224294},{"subjectID":"yg56lwljnr","prolificID":"6719280d44c996e04f9a5475","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25171d097020dac2f28","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980426102,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"108","question":"What are some pieces of media (books, movies, music, etc.) that have influenced how you think or see the world?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":4387,"timeElapsed":228686},{"subjectID":"yg56lwljnr","prolificID":"6719280d44c996e04f9a5475","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25171d097020dac2f28","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980433774,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"108","question":"What are some pieces of media (books, movies, music, etc.) that have influenced how you think or see the world?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":2,"rt":7667,"timeElapsed":236358},{"subjectID":"yg56lwljnr","prolificID":"6719280d44c996e04f9a5475","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25171d097020dac2f28","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980443397,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"108","question":"What are some pieces of media (books, movies, music, etc.) that have influenced how you think or see the world?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":28,"rt":9620,"timeElapsed":245982},{"subjectID":"yg56lwljnr","prolificID":"6719280d44c996e04f9a5475","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25171d097020dac2f28","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980450668,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"108","question":"What are some pieces of media (books, movies, music, etc.) that have influenced how you think or see the world?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":7266,"timeElapsed":253253},{"subjectID":"yg56lwljnr","prolificID":"6719280d44c996e04f9a5475","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25171d097020dac2f28","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980468477,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"88","question":"If you could cook just one dish to express who you are to someone, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":17,"rt":16288,"timeElapsed":271062},{"subjectID":"yg56lwljnr","prolificID":"6719280d44c996e04f9a5475","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25171d097020dac2f28","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980475614,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"88","question":"If you could cook just one dish to express who you are to someone, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":15,"rt":7131,"timeElapsed":278198},{"subjectID":"yg56lwljnr","prolificID":"6719280d44c996e04f9a5475","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25171d097020dac2f28","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980483182,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"88","question":"If you could cook just one dish to express who you are to someone, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":29,"rt":7563,"timeElapsed":285767},{"subjectID":"yg56lwljnr","prolificID":"6719280d44c996e04f9a5475","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25171d097020dac2f28","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980486164,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"88","question":"If you could cook just one dish to express who you are to someone, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":34,"rt":2979,"timeElapsed":288749},{"subjectID":"yg56lwljnr","prolificID":"6719280d44c996e04f9a5475","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25171d097020dac2f28","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980496181,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"88","question":"If you could cook just one dish to express who you are to someone, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":7,"rt":10012,"timeElapsed":298766},{"subjectID":"yg56lwljnr","prolificID":"6719280d44c996e04f9a5475","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25171d097020dac2f28","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980499510,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"88","question":"If you could cook just one dish to express who you are to someone, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":5,"rt":3324,"timeElapsed":302095},{"subjectID":"yg56lwljnr","prolificID":"6719280d44c996e04f9a5475","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25171d097020dac2f28","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980508796,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"88","question":"If you could cook just one dish to express who you are to someone, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":7,"rt":9282,"timeElapsed":311381},{"subjectID":"yg56lwljnr","prolificID":"6719280d44c996e04f9a5475","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25171d097020dac2f28","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980518342,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"If you could cook just one dish to express who you are to someone, what would it be?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":9542,"timeElapsed":320927},{"subjectID":"yg56lwljnr","prolificID":"6719280d44c996e04f9a5475","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25171d097020dac2f28","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980527453,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"88","question":"If you could cook just one dish to express who you are to someone, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":17,"rt":9107,"timeElapsed":330038},{"subjectID":"yg56lwljnr","prolificID":"6719280d44c996e04f9a5475","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25171d097020dac2f28","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980536686,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"88","question":"If you could cook just one dish to express who you are to someone, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":9228,"timeElapsed":339271},{"subjectID":"yg56lwljnr","prolificID":"6719280d44c996e04f9a5475","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25171d097020dac2f28","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980554254,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"201","question":"When was the last time you went to the movies? What did you see? Did you like it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":16111,"timeElapsed":356839},{"subjectID":"yg56lwljnr","prolificID":"6719280d44c996e04f9a5475","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25171d097020dac2f28","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980563100,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"201","question":"When was the last time you went to the movies? What did you see? Did you like it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":34,"rt":8842,"timeElapsed":365685},{"subjectID":"yg56lwljnr","prolificID":"6719280d44c996e04f9a5475","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25171d097020dac2f28","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980570126,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"201","question":"When was the last time you went to the movies? What did you see? Did you like it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":20,"rt":7020,"timeElapsed":372711},{"subjectID":"yg56lwljnr","prolificID":"6719280d44c996e04f9a5475","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25171d097020dac2f28","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980573540,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"201","question":"When was the last time you went to the movies? What did you see? Did you like it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":25,"rt":3411,"timeElapsed":376125},{"subjectID":"yg56lwljnr","prolificID":"6719280d44c996e04f9a5475","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25171d097020dac2f28","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980579117,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"201","question":"When was the last time you went to the movies? What did you see? Did you like it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":4,"rt":5574,"timeElapsed":381702},{"subjectID":"yg56lwljnr","prolificID":"6719280d44c996e04f9a5475","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25171d097020dac2f28","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980596413,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"201","question":"When was the last time you went to the movies? What did you see? Did you like it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":10,"rt":17291,"timeElapsed":398997},{"subjectID":"yg56lwljnr","prolificID":"6719280d44c996e04f9a5475","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25171d097020dac2f28","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980601581,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"201","question":"When was the last time you went to the movies? What did you see? Did you like it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":6,"rt":5163,"timeElapsed":404166},{"subjectID":"yg56lwljnr","prolificID":"6719280d44c996e04f9a5475","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25171d097020dac2f28","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980606381,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"201","question":"When was the last time you went to the movies? What did you see? Did you like it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":17,"rt":4795,"timeElapsed":408965},{"subjectID":"yg56lwljnr","prolificID":"6719280d44c996e04f9a5475","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25171d097020dac2f28","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980610509,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"201","question":"When was the last time you went to the movies? What did you see? Did you like it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":27,"rt":4124,"timeElapsed":413094},{"subjectID":"yg56lwljnr","prolificID":"6719280d44c996e04f9a5475","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25171d097020dac2f28","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980621741,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"171","question":"Have you ever tried to learn a TikTok dance? How did it go?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":18,"rt":9704,"timeElapsed":424325},{"subjectID":"yg56lwljnr","prolificID":"6719280d44c996e04f9a5475","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25171d097020dac2f28","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980625500,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"171","question":"Have you ever tried to learn a TikTok dance? How did it go?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":20,"rt":3755,"timeElapsed":428085},{"subjectID":"yg56lwljnr","prolificID":"6719280d44c996e04f9a5475","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25171d097020dac2f28","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980631317,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"171","question":"Have you ever tried to learn a TikTok dance? How did it go?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":5812,"timeElapsed":433902},{"subjectID":"yg56lwljnr","prolificID":"6719280d44c996e04f9a5475","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25171d097020dac2f28","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980633885,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"171","question":"Have you ever tried to learn a TikTok dance? How did it go?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":2563,"timeElapsed":436470},{"subjectID":"yg56lwljnr","prolificID":"6719280d44c996e04f9a5475","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25171d097020dac2f28","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980643468,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"171","question":"Have you ever tried to learn a TikTok dance? How did it go?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":11,"rt":9580,"timeElapsed":446053},{"subjectID":"yg56lwljnr","prolificID":"6719280d44c996e04f9a5475","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25171d097020dac2f28","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980647125,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"171","question":"Have you ever tried to learn a TikTok dance? How did it go?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":10,"rt":3652,"timeElapsed":449710},{"subjectID":"yg56lwljnr","prolificID":"6719280d44c996e04f9a5475","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25171d097020dac2f28","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980652877,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"171","question":"Have you ever tried to learn a TikTok dance? How did it go?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":3,"rt":5747,"timeElapsed":455462},{"subjectID":"yg56lwljnr","prolificID":"6719280d44c996e04f9a5475","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25171d097020dac2f28","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980660989,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"171","question":"Have you ever tried to learn a TikTok dance? How did it go?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":8108,"timeElapsed":463574},{"subjectID":"yg56lwljnr","prolificID":"6719280d44c996e04f9a5475","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25171d097020dac2f28","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980666045,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"171","question":"Have you ever tried to learn a TikTok dance? How did it go?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":18,"rt":5051,"timeElapsed":468630},{"subjectID":"yg56lwljnr","prolificID":"6719280d44c996e04f9a5475","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25171d097020dac2f28","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980681412,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"244","question":"Are you typically early for things or do you often run late? Has this ever gotten you into trouble or helped you out in some way?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":21,"rt":14040,"timeElapsed":483997},{"subjectID":"yg56lwljnr","prolificID":"6719280d44c996e04f9a5475","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25171d097020dac2f28","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980684795,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"244","question":"Are you typically early for things or do you often run late? Has this ever gotten you into trouble or helped you out in some way?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":23,"rt":3379,"timeElapsed":487380},{"subjectID":"yg56lwljnr","prolificID":"6719280d44c996e04f9a5475","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25171d097020dac2f28","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980692708,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"244","question":"Are you typically early for things or do you often run late? Has this ever gotten you into trouble or helped you out in some way?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":43,"rt":7911,"timeElapsed":495293},{"subjectID":"yg56lwljnr","prolificID":"6719280d44c996e04f9a5475","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25171d097020dac2f28","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980699572,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"244","question":"Are you typically early for things or do you often run late? Has this ever gotten you into trouble or helped you out in some way?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":6860,"timeElapsed":502157},{"subjectID":"yg56lwljnr","prolificID":"6719280d44c996e04f9a5475","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25171d097020dac2f28","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980707045,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"244","question":"Are you typically early for things or do you often run late? Has this ever gotten you into trouble or helped you out in some way?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":6,"rt":7468,"timeElapsed":509630},{"subjectID":"yg56lwljnr","prolificID":"6719280d44c996e04f9a5475","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25171d097020dac2f28","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980712372,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"244","question":"Are you typically early for things or do you often run late? Has this ever gotten you into trouble or helped you out in some way?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":5,"rt":5323,"timeElapsed":514957},{"subjectID":"yg56lwljnr","prolificID":"6719280d44c996e04f9a5475","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25171d097020dac2f28","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980721133,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"244","question":"Are you typically early for things or do you often run late? Has this ever gotten you into trouble or helped you out in some way?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":13,"rt":8756,"timeElapsed":523718},{"subjectID":"yg56lwljnr","prolificID":"6719280d44c996e04f9a5475","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25171d097020dac2f28","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980735524,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"244","question":"Are you typically early for things or do you often run late? Has this ever gotten you into trouble or helped you out in some way?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":14387,"timeElapsed":538109},{"subjectID":"yg56lwljnr","prolificID":"6719280d44c996e04f9a5475","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25171d097020dac2f28","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980741111,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Are you typically early for things or do you often run late? Has this ever gotten you into trouble or helped you out in some way?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":5582,"timeElapsed":543695},{"subjectID":"yg56lwljnr","prolificID":"6719280d44c996e04f9a5475","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25171d097020dac2f28","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980750015,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"244","question":"Are you typically early for things or do you often run late? Has this ever gotten you into trouble or helped you out in some way?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":8899,"timeElapsed":552600},{"subjectID":"yg56lwljnr","prolificID":"6719280d44c996e04f9a5475","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25171d097020dac2f28","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980762065,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"176","question":"What is your strategy for eating a really messy taco?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":14,"rt":10883,"timeElapsed":564649},{"subjectID":"yg56lwljnr","prolificID":"6719280d44c996e04f9a5475","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25171d097020dac2f28","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980768346,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"176","question":"What is your strategy for eating a really messy taco?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":15,"rt":6278,"timeElapsed":570931},{"subjectID":"yg56lwljnr","prolificID":"6719280d44c996e04f9a5475","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25171d097020dac2f28","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980776883,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"176","question":"What is your strategy for eating a really messy taco?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":15,"rt":8534,"timeElapsed":579468},{"subjectID":"yg56lwljnr","prolificID":"6719280d44c996e04f9a5475","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25171d097020dac2f28","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980780095,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"176","question":"What is your strategy for eating a really messy taco?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":15,"rt":3208,"timeElapsed":582680},{"subjectID":"yg56lwljnr","prolificID":"6719280d44c996e04f9a5475","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25171d097020dac2f28","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980789477,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"176","question":"What is your strategy for eating a really messy taco?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":10,"rt":9377,"timeElapsed":592061},{"subjectID":"yg56lwljnr","prolificID":"6719280d44c996e04f9a5475","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25171d097020dac2f28","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980793436,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"176","question":"What is your strategy for eating a really messy taco?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":9,"rt":3956,"timeElapsed":596021},{"subjectID":"yg56lwljnr","prolificID":"6719280d44c996e04f9a5475","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25171d097020dac2f28","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980797492,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"176","question":"What is your strategy for eating a really messy taco?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":4,"rt":4051,"timeElapsed":600077},{"subjectID":"yg56lwljnr","prolificID":"6719280d44c996e04f9a5475","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25171d097020dac2f28","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980802814,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"176","question":"What is your strategy for eating a really messy taco?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":10,"rt":5318,"timeElapsed":605399},{"subjectID":"yg56lwljnr","prolificID":"6719280d44c996e04f9a5475","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25171d097020dac2f28","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980808037,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"176","question":"What is your strategy for eating a really messy taco?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":11,"rt":5219,"timeElapsed":610622},{"subjectID":"yg56lwljnr","prolificID":"6719280d44c996e04f9a5475","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25171d097020dac2f28","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980823380,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"67","question":"What role or responsibility did you have in your family that you later realized was not typical for your age?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":13895,"timeElapsed":625965},{"subjectID":"yg56lwljnr","prolificID":"6719280d44c996e04f9a5475","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25171d097020dac2f28","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980829460,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"67","question":"What role or responsibility did you have in your family that you later realized was not typical for your age?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":6076,"timeElapsed":632045},{"subjectID":"yg56lwljnr","prolificID":"6719280d44c996e04f9a5475","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25171d097020dac2f28","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980834148,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"67","question":"What role or responsibility did you have in your family that you later realized was not typical for your age?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":4684,"timeElapsed":636733},{"subjectID":"yg56lwljnr","prolificID":"6719280d44c996e04f9a5475","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25171d097020dac2f28","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980837101,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"67","question":"What role or responsibility did you have in your family that you later realized was not typical for your age?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":2947,"timeElapsed":639686},{"subjectID":"yg56lwljnr","prolificID":"6719280d44c996e04f9a5475","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25171d097020dac2f28","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980844220,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"67","question":"What role or responsibility did you have in your family that you later realized was not typical for your age?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":7113,"timeElapsed":646805},{"subjectID":"yg56lwljnr","prolificID":"6719280d44c996e04f9a5475","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25171d097020dac2f28","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980847101,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"67","question":"What role or responsibility did you have in your family that you later realized was not typical for your age?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":2876,"timeElapsed":649686},{"subjectID":"yg56lwljnr","prolificID":"6719280d44c996e04f9a5475","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25171d097020dac2f28","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980865549,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"67","question":"What role or responsibility did you have in your family that you later realized was not typical for your age?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":18443,"timeElapsed":668133},{"subjectID":"yg56lwljnr","prolificID":"6719280d44c996e04f9a5475","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25171d097020dac2f28","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980874468,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"67","question":"What role or responsibility did you have in your family that you later realized was not typical for your age?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":8916,"timeElapsed":677053},{"subjectID":"yg56lwljnr","prolificID":"6719280d44c996e04f9a5475","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25171d097020dac2f28","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980879740,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"67","question":"What role or responsibility did you have in your family that you later realized was not typical for your age?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":5268,"timeElapsed":682325},{"subjectID":"yg56lwljnr","prolificID":"6719280d44c996e04f9a5475","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25171d097020dac2f28","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980889092,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"145","question":"Describe the most recent gift you received. Who was it from and what was the context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":6,"rt":8024,"timeElapsed":691677},{"subjectID":"yg56lwljnr","prolificID":"6719280d44c996e04f9a5475","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25171d097020dac2f28","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980893173,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"145","question":"Describe the most recent gift you received. Who was it from and what was the context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":9,"rt":4074,"timeElapsed":695758},{"subjectID":"yg56lwljnr","prolificID":"6719280d44c996e04f9a5475","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25171d097020dac2f28","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980899124,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"145","question":"Describe the most recent gift you received. Who was it from and what was the context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":22,"rt":5947,"timeElapsed":701709},{"subjectID":"yg56lwljnr","prolificID":"6719280d44c996e04f9a5475","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25171d097020dac2f28","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980901645,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"145","question":"Describe the most recent gift you received. Who was it from and what was the context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":24,"rt":2515,"timeElapsed":704230},{"subjectID":"yg56lwljnr","prolificID":"6719280d44c996e04f9a5475","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25171d097020dac2f28","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980908372,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"145","question":"Describe the most recent gift you received. Who was it from and what was the context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":6,"rt":6723,"timeElapsed":710957},{"subjectID":"yg56lwljnr","prolificID":"6719280d44c996e04f9a5475","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25171d097020dac2f28","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980911828,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"145","question":"Describe the most recent gift you received. Who was it from and what was the context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":7,"rt":3450,"timeElapsed":714413},{"subjectID":"yg56lwljnr","prolificID":"6719280d44c996e04f9a5475","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25171d097020dac2f28","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980921860,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"145","question":"Describe the most recent gift you received. Who was it from and what was the context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":26,"rt":10028,"timeElapsed":724445},{"subjectID":"yg56lwljnr","prolificID":"6719280d44c996e04f9a5475","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25171d097020dac2f28","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980928460,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"145","question":"Describe the most recent gift you received. Who was it from and what was the context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":6595,"timeElapsed":731044},{"subjectID":"yg56lwljnr","prolificID":"6719280d44c996e04f9a5475","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25171d097020dac2f28","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980934683,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"145","question":"Describe the most recent gift you received. Who was it from and what was the context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":24,"rt":6219,"timeElapsed":737268},{"subjectID":"yg56lwljnr","prolificID":"6719280d44c996e04f9a5475","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25171d097020dac2f28","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980949468,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"114","question":"What are your personal life or career priorities?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":13209,"timeElapsed":752053},{"subjectID":"yg56lwljnr","prolificID":"6719280d44c996e04f9a5475","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25171d097020dac2f28","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980952332,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"114","question":"What are your personal life or career priorities?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":2859,"timeElapsed":754917},{"subjectID":"yg56lwljnr","prolificID":"6719280d44c996e04f9a5475","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25171d097020dac2f28","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980956926,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"114","question":"What are your personal life or career priorities?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":4590,"timeElapsed":759510},{"subjectID":"yg56lwljnr","prolificID":"6719280d44c996e04f9a5475","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25171d097020dac2f28","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980959709,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"114","question":"What are your personal life or career priorities?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":2778,"timeElapsed":762294},{"subjectID":"yg56lwljnr","prolificID":"6719280d44c996e04f9a5475","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25171d097020dac2f28","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980967372,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"114","question":"What are your personal life or career priorities?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":28,"rt":7658,"timeElapsed":769956},{"subjectID":"yg56lwljnr","prolificID":"6719280d44c996e04f9a5475","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25171d097020dac2f28","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980970604,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"114","question":"What are your personal life or career priorities?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":28,"rt":3228,"timeElapsed":773189},{"subjectID":"yg56lwljnr","prolificID":"6719280d44c996e04f9a5475","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25171d097020dac2f28","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980975363,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"114","question":"What are your personal life or career priorities?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":25,"rt":4756,"timeElapsed":777948},{"subjectID":"yg56lwljnr","prolificID":"6719280d44c996e04f9a5475","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25171d097020dac2f28","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980981524,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"114","question":"What are your personal life or career priorities?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":6158,"timeElapsed":784109},{"subjectID":"yg56lwljnr","prolificID":"6719280d44c996e04f9a5475","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25171d097020dac2f28","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980986135,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"114","question":"What are your personal life or career priorities?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":4606,"timeElapsed":788720}]